[theme music playing]
[Emilia] Kill Madrigal in front of us.
[Julio] Shoot the dog!
-[gunshot]
-[grunts]
[Ivy] I won't taint my hands
just to prove my loyalty!
The next time you accuse
your biggest investor,
I won't even need to think twice about
siding with your greatest rival.
But for now, my word is as good as gold.
[Jepoy] You have
to get out of here, Jepoy.
Ivy needs you right now.
I need to endure this for Ivy.
[Julio] Since I can't rely on you
when it comes to Miss Aguas,
I want you to do something else
to get rid of all my problems.
[Diego] Miss Camia,
are you expecting company?
-No.
-[man] There are bodyguards.
[Arnaldo] So what? Are you scared?
-[thuds]
-[car alarm blares]
-[Diego] Miss Camia, get in.
-[Camia] What's going on?
[Ivy] I want you all to be alert
and more careful.
I need to save Jepoy.
[Diego] I will never forgive myself
if something bad happens to you.
And I won't forgive myself if Jepoy dies!
[Diego] Ivy, I know I can't stop you.
I will help you.
[Ivy] I'll find him, Diego.
I need to go to the Ardientes.
What did you do to Jepoy?
Is he still alive?
Where did you move him?
Where did you take him?
You will tell me the name of your boss.
If you don't,
I'll drill a hole in your skull
until your brain gushes out!
[Arnaldo] Hello, Mom?
Any news on Madrigal?
Who's his boss? Who does he work for?
[Emilia] Did you hear what I said?
Madrigal folded.
Probably, he couldn't stand the torture.
So, he'll start talking
and he won't try to escape again.
Good.
I'm coming there.
I'll clean up the mess
that Madrigal caused.
Don't bother, son.
Your grandpa and I will take care of it.
And this traitor will surely confess.
-[Arnaldo] Okay, enjoy.
-All right.
Is that about Madrigal?
Yes.
But that traitor is not talking yet.
[sighing] That bastard.
That Madrigal is such a bastard.
Don't worry.
The time is running out
for the traitors of this family.
-Let's go inside?
-Yes, please.
[William] Uh, Congressman and Mrs. Emilia
have an emergency to attend to,
but your beloved governor
is ready to listen to all your concerns.
It's better if those Ardientes
don't come back here!
That family is the scourge of this town!
-[men] He's right!
-[William] Hold on.
Calm down, everyone.
You're just defending your bosses!
Aren't you one of their lapdogs?!
-[men] Yeah! He's right!
-[crowd clamoring]
-[William] Hold on, everyone.
-[clamoring]
Please calm down. Have your seats!
Don't start any trouble, everyone!
[clamoring]
[William] Hold on!
What are you doing, huh?!
Why are you just standing around?
Give me the mic!
[Arnaldo] Security!
Arrest the agitators!
Mayor Arnaldo is so full
of himself, Governor.
The arrogance of the Ardientes
will bring their demise.
[clamoring]
Let's go.
[Arnaldo] To my constituents,
please have your seats.
To my constituents…
to the loyal supporters of the Ardientes…
as long as I'm in power…
no traitor or rebel
can defeat the Ardientes!
Viva Ardiente!
-Viva Ardiente!
-[townsfolk] Viva Ardiente!
Viva Ardiente!
[club music playing]
Maybe he wants company. Relax.
Hi, I'm Lovely.
Hi, I'm Honey.
Hello.
We asked you to handle
the crowd just once…
and then that happened.
Anyway, where are the earnings
from the gambling den?
We have yet to reach our quota,
Congressman.
[chuckles]
Damn it, Alvarez.
You know we need that money
for the next election.
Why don't you take my advice?
You know,
just disappear like vapor into thin air
and don't come back
until I tell you to do so.
I will never leave.
And let me make this clear
once and for all, Congressman.
I'm not your lapdog.
Be careful with your words, Alvarez.
It's me who you're talking to.
[chuckles]
A typical Ardiente.
Always backstabbing one another…
but united when someone
threatens the family.
And yet, you're all cowards
when facing criticism.
If you only heard the accusations
people have leveled against you.
That's the farthest you can go, Governor…
unless you want to end up
like the ones who dared
to oppose the Ardientes.
[foreboding music playing]
Madrigal was my bodyguard for two years.
Sometimes, the people you trust the most
are the ones who betray you.
That's why I believe that loyalty
is the most important thing
you can give to someone.
It's even more important than love.
You, Mr. Mayor…
You've been a wonderful friend to me…
a loyal friend.
But, Miss Aguas…
I don't want to be your friend.
I want you ever since.
I want us to be together.
[tense music playing]
Mr. Mayor.
We cannot always get
what we want when we want it.
Good night.
[Arnaldo] Oh, Diego!
What are you doing here?
It's none of your business.
I came for Ivy.
But for what?
To persuade her to side
with you and Camia?
When will you stop being foolish, huh?!
It's never foolish
to protect innocent people
from the Ardientes!
Oh, really?
And how exactly will you do that, huh?
You can't win.
What's up your sleeve? Your witnesses?
From what I remember, they're all dead.
-You bastard!
-[Arnaldo grunting]
-[security] Sir, stop it!
-[Diego] Shame on you!
[security] Diego, stop it!
Let go of me!
Try to ruin the Ardiente name again,
and your witnesses won't be
the only ones dead.
I'll kill you too.
[security] Look out for him.
Stop!
Stop it! What are you doing here, huh?!
You! Get out!
Out!
Leave my property.
And spare me from your plans with Camia
because I don't want to be involved
with either of you!
Do you understand?!
Out!
Now!
Mr. Mayor, what happened?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I can't believe him.
Thank you.
[Camia] Check all the gates,
doors, and windows.
Make sure that Raul
can't enter this house.
[security] Yes, ma'am.
Camia, we just moved in.
I'm sure Raul won't bother us here.
Carlotta, Raul is lying.
He can't possibly care about my safety.
He locked me up for so long.
That man is heartless.
[Carlotta] But, what if…
he's telling the truth about saving you?
If that's the case, I'll thank him.
But I know why he's doing this,
to regain my trust.
But I won't make the same mistake.
Aha!
So, this is what the Ardientes
have been hiding.
This is why they left the charity event…
and made me look like an idiot.
So, who are you?
How did you betray the Ardientes?
Did they treat you horribly?
Well, the Ardientes are really arrogant,
so I can't blame you.
[man] Governor,
here's the collected money.
Ah!
Very good.
[chuckling]
Go ahead, Ardientes…
-Keep on belittling me.
-[man chuckles]
I'll drain all your wealth.
[laughs]
Put it back there.
[chuckles]
-[all] Cheers.
-Shot!
[Raul] Wait, I forgot the salt.
Let me put it here.
[Honey] Go, go, go!
[Natalie] Excuse me. Mind if I join you?
In the flesh.
Natalie?
[Natalie] Okay, ladies, playtime is over.
Get out.
-I said, get out.
-[Raul] Later, girls.
[Raul chuckles]
Hmm!
What are we having?
Mr. Mayor, we need to do this
so you won't get bruises.
[Arnaldo] I can take care of it.
But thanks for getting rid
of that bastard.
It's his fault for storming here.
[Arnaldo] You know what,
you've always been loyal to me.
It feels like…
there's this thing between us.
And I know…
I'm not the only one…
who feels the same way.
So I was thinking…
why don't we make this official?
I mean, think about it.
No one can stop us.
Natalie is gone, and we're both single.
In my opinion, I think it's time for us
to pick up where we left off.
Arnaldo, I'll be right back.
Miss Aguas.
Stay.
Well, whatever that is…
I still want you.
You said you can take care of yourself.
Good night, Mr. Mayor.
Well, I went to Paris,
and I went to Berlin.
And Berlin somehow became a favorite.
I loved it so much,
I almost didn't come back.
That's the thing. Why did you come back?
Everyone comes back for a reason.
Until now,
I ponder how my dad died so suddenly.
You know, those kinds of death…
It's not by accident.
I know someone had him killed,
and I want to know who it is.
But let's not talk about that now.
You know what?
You're actually looking a lot hotter
than I remember, Uncle Raul.
Or should I call you Raul?
In fact, you're looking a lot hotter
than someone I know.
Someone named Arnaldo, perhaps?
I'm actually glad
that I came here tonight.
I think I'll come here more often now.
Really? [chuckles]
Cheers.
[William] Well, look at this.
You have the governor as your babysitter.
Tell me who your boss is…
so I could earn a brownie point
from Julio.
His grandson, Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente…
a charismatic leader
and idol of the masses…
and has a beautiful woman by his side.
But you know…
I'm more than satisfied
to get a taste of that woman.
Just for once…
I get to see how it feels
to be Arnaldo Ardiente.
[line ringing]
Benjie.
Find out where Ivy Aguas lives.
Yeah.
Bring her to me.
Alvarez is testing my patience.
That's why I tasked him
to look after Madrigal.
[sighs]
Oh!
-Good morning, Miss Aguas!
-[Ivy] Good morning.
[Julio] You're a sight for sore eyes.
I didn't know you were
joining us for breakfast.
I came to see Mr. Mayor, Congressman.
Good morning.
-I have something for you.
-[Arnaldo] Well, thank you.
Please, sit down.
I had an altercation with
everyone's favorite bastard,
and Ivy took care of me.
Well, you better make sure
that Diego had it worse.
You have nothing to worry about, Grandpa.
And also, I'll be gracing
an opening of a museum
in Manila.
Ivy's gonna be my date.
Date?
Um…
Does this mean Natalie is ancient history?
[chuckles]
Well, I think it's better
not to talk about her…
especially if I crowned Ivy
my future first lady.
Affairs of the heart, I leave to you.
Future first lady?
Can't I be your future date first?
Please, have some coffee or tea.
Thank you.
[Julio] Madrigal, I give you two choices.
I give you a minute.
Tell me what I wanna hear, or you die.
In one minute, remember.
So, are you going to spill the beans, huh?
Cover him now.
-Go.
-[spurting]
[Julio] Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five…
[coughing]
[gasping]
Madrigal.
Madrigal! Can you hear me?!
This is your last chance.
I'll count to 10.
If you still don't confess…
this water and piece of cloth
will drown you to death!
Now just to be sure.
I'll count to 10.
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
six, five… Last chance!
Four, three, two, one! Drown him!
[spurting]
-[Jepoy mumbling]
-What was that?
Take it off.
-[stuttering] I'm going to talk!
-[Julio] What?
-I'm going to talk.
-[Julio] Good!
Give me the answer I want.
Who's your boss?
[Jepoy coughing]
[phone ringing]
Yes, Mr. Mayor?
Hello, Miss Aguas.
Yes, I'm sorry. I'm afraid
we have to cancel our date.
The congressman and Mom need me here.
Madrigal is finally talking.
Who is he working for?
[Julio] Give me the answer I want.
[gasping] The governor. The governor.
-Who?
-Alvarez!
[tense music playing]
[Carlotta] Ivy, I already
asked Diego to come down.
Thank you.
Ivy, I'm sorry. I'm just worried,
so I went to you.
-I didn't know Arnaldo--
-Diego…
I should be the one to apologize.
I'm sorry for sending you away last night.
You know that I need information
to save Jepoy.
But, Ivy, I don't want you
playing with fire.
I won't get burned in the game.
Can't you just…
Can we first think this through?
We can't, Diego.
I can't stop.
Many things happened to the Ardientes.
They've been exposed and sued,
but they're still free.
They still have Jepoy.
I can't stop now.
Because in every minute I waste,
the Ardientes are taking a step forward.
The war has just begun, Diego.
Ivy's war has just begun.
That's why I need
to stay close to Arnaldo…
so I'll know the plans of the Ardientes.
We will win this war,
and we will save Jepoy.
[Diego] If you're going to fight…
then I'll fight too.
As long as the Ardientes are in power,
they can't be brought down.
Someone should fight them head-on.
What do you mean?
I will run for governor.
Ivy, times have changed.
The people aren't ignorant like before.
Many are aware of the cruelty
of the Ardientes.
And now, I will lead them towards change.
I will do everything
in my power to help you win.
And bring downfall to the Ardientes.
For a new Poblacion Ardiente.
[Arnaldo] Grandpa.
-[man grunting]
-Speak up!
Congressman.
The governor has been holding
a grudge against you.
We used hear him say
that he's enduring all your hurtful words
while he drains your money.
Then show me the money.
Return every cent
that Alvarez stole from me.
Governor Alvarez has it all, Congressman.
Arnaldo.
You know what to do.
Have mercy, Congressman!
I already told the truth!
Please have mercy! I have a family!
Jepoy wouldn't point Alvarez
without a reason.
If that's the case…
we need to find out why he chose Alvarez.
Here, look at this.
Governor William Alvarez
has very good credentials,
and yet he's being pushed around
by the Ardientes.
Alvarez manages the largest
charity institution in Ardiente.
Many corrupt officials
use charity institutions
to hide their ill-gotten wealth.
Does Alvarez have a hidden
grudge against the Ardientes?
That's why he's stealing from them.
I'll look for Alvarez.
Arnaldo also needs
to know this information.
Governor Alvarez.
[Arnaldo] The good news
is Madrigal was right.
Alvarez has been stealing money
from my family.
But the bad news is that Alvarez is gone…
-along with the stolen money.
-[maid screaming]
Where is your boss? Where is Alvarez?
-I don't know, sir.
-Search upstairs.
[goon 1] Stay right there!
[goon 2] Sir, the vault is empty.
[phone ringing]
Negative.
Alvarez is not here,
and neither is our money.
[Ivy] So, Madrigal's confession
was useless.
Unfortunately.
Then, what's next for Madrigal?
You know what we do to people
or things that are useless…
they get disposed of.
[Ivy] You know, Mr. Mayor…
I have a feeling
that you'll still need Madrigal.
You know why?
I did my own research, and look at this.
Governor Alvarez isn't just a thief.
Governor Alvarez is also
funneling government funds
into his charity institution.
You know what that means?
You can sue Governor Alvarez,
and Madrigal will be
your number one witness.
Okay, go on.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
[Diego] Ivy.
I went to a house
featured in an online article.
It's confirmed.
This is the rest house
of Alvarez in Tagaytay.
Okay, thank you.
[Arnaldo] Who was that?
My own source of intelligence.
Well, Mr. Mayor…
like what I said…
sue Governor Alvarez…
and I'll tell you where he is.
And Madrigal?
He's going to be your number one witness.
Can I join you?
Please.
You are of no use now, Madrigal.
Adios.
Make him kneel.
Well…
-[cocks gun]
-Well, do it!
Lower your guns.
We can't kill him right now.
And why is that?
We'll use him as a witness against Alvarez
for stealing government funds.
[Julio] And how the hell
are we going to do that?!
We don't even know where he is.
Well, good thing I have an idea
about his whereabouts.
No problem, Mr. Mayor.
Good.
[Ivy] They can't kill you, Jepoy,
because I won't let them.
I'll do everything in my power
just to keep you alive.
[Emilia] This can't be
happening, Aunt Claire.
We have to do something about it.
Don't worry, Emilia. I'll help you.
Arnaldo will eventually return
to his senses.
Well, what are you two doing?
-Plotting my murder?
-Of course not, Papa.
I'm worried about Arnaldo and Ivy.
What about them?
You shouldn't despise something
just because you cannot have it.
But, Papa, future First Lady?
You know, I must admit before,
I wanted Ivy for Arnaldo
because of her money.
But that was before, Papa.
Now, loyalty is more important
to me than money.
Emilia, I trust your son.
And besides, if Ivy Aguas
is truly the enemy…
then we need to have her by our side.
To quote my favorite philosopher…
"To win the war,
keep your friends close
and your enemies closer."
You two should really learn…
instead of gossiping all the time.
That's what you think, Julio.
[Julio scoffs]
I heard you, Claire!
[tense music]
[suppressed gunshot]
[suppressed gunshots]
-Mayor!
-How's life, Governor?
What's up?
Good thing I caught up with you
before you escaped your crimes.
Crimes?
Against who? The Ardientes?
If you're talking about
the spare change I took,
that's nothing compared
to your ill-gotten wealth.
Such hurtful words.
Tell it to the Congressman, Governor.
All right, then.
I better get going, Mayor.
What's wrong?
Do it. Pull the trigger.
Don't think that I won't pull the trigger
for your beloved mayor!
Come on! Shoot me!
[gunshot]
[Arnaldo] After him!
More than 10 million pesos
were retrieved by Mayor Arnaldo Torillo
among the belongings
of Governor Alvarez earlier today.
However, the governor managed
to escape from the scene.
A manhunt operation is underway
for him to face
his graft and corruption raps.
Now that they got
what they wanted from Alvarez,
when will they release Jepoy?
Why are they still keeping him?
Lily…
This wasn't supposed to happen.
We have to put an end to this.
Many were affected by this,
like Governor Alvarez,
-as well as--
-[Camia] Alvarez is a criminal.
He has to answer
not just to the Ardientes,
but to the people as well.
But what about Jepoy?
What about Jepoy?
He's still keeping my secrets.
I don't know what the Ardientes
are doing to him.
How long can he fight?
How long are they going to torture him?
[Camia] Lily, Jepoy zeroed in on Alvarez
because it's his way of fighting back.
I know you're feeling guilty,
but for now, it's better that Alvarez
is the one being targeted, not you.
Go on. Release him.
-[Julio whoops]
-[grunting]
Easy, boy. Easy.
You know what, Madrigal? You were right.
You were telling me the truth.
I finally got the money
that Alvarez stole from me.
Just one question.
I'm just wondering…
How did he become your boss?
He's not my boss.
I suspected him to be a traitor
to the Ardiente family.
-That's why I bugged him.
-[chuckles]
[Julio] Why didn't you tell us
immediately, huh?
Why did you choose to be tortured
and experience
all this pain and suffering?
You know, this is
a big question mark in my head.
-Why?
-Because it's useless.
Huh?
Because Ardientes have this nature…
you're all bloodthirsty to kill.
[Jepoy breathing deeply]
Now, let's not get
over ourselves, Madrigal.
You helped me, I'll give you that.
But just because you helped me
doesn't mean you can judge me!
You don't know me!
You don't know me, Madrigal!
But still, I thank you…
because you did that to protect my family.
I'm loyal to you.
I proved that already.
So when will you release me?
I would like to reward you, Madrigal.
I really would!
But not just yet.
Not yet.
Uh… Excuse me, dear.
I'll just go upstairs.
Okay, Mom.
Diego, are you sure you weren't followed?
I'm sure. My investigation went smoothly.
Thank you so much for finding Alvarez.
That really helped us to save Jepoy.
But, Diego, I hope that was the last.
What do you mean?
Too many people are getting involved
and getting hurt in my plans.
I don't want you to also get into trouble.
Ivy, I know you feel guilty
for what happened to Alvarez and Jepoy.
But it's me, Ivy.
We were there for each other
since childhood.
What are you afraid of?
I'm scared that you might also get caught.
If they catch you,
they might torture you too.
I can't forgive myself
if that happens, Diego.
Ivy, I want you to trust me.
Let me protect you
because there's nothing
I wouldn't do for you.
[Emilia] Hear me out, Aunt Claire.
That Alvarez is losing
his family's wealth,
became a gambling addict,
and now stole from our family.
That only means one thing, Auntie.
Alvarez is out, and Emilia is so in!
Emilia, darling.
How sure are you
that you will be reinstated
by your dad as governor?
Auntie, I won't wait for that anymore.
I'll reinstate myself.
[Raul] Emilia.
Congratulations.
I heard that you'll be back in office.
Honestly, you're really meant for that
because you're the queen of this town.
Raul, thank you for the kind words.
But, you'll soon be
the king of this town too.
Me as the king? I doubt it.
Congressman Julio and Arnaldo
are the only kings here.
As for me, let's just say
that I'm an escort.
But at least…
I'm the escort of
Queen Emilia Ardiente-Torillo.
You know, Raul,
I know you're being sarcastic,
but I'll take you seriously for now.
All right, I'll go ahead.
Bye.
You're falling for his smooth talks again.
Auntie, Raul has changed a lot, right?
-What if he hasn't?
-I'd like to see him try.
That's if he wants to have more
of his mistresses killed.
Governor Emilia is back.
I've been waiting all night.
I thought you weren't coming.
I'm sorry. I couldn't find the right time.
Many things happened at the house.
Like what?
You know, Natalie, if you think
that I had something to do
with your father's death…
you approached the wrong person.
You're so defensive. Fine, I'm sorry.
If I give you what you want…
will you tell me what you know?
Hmm?
[indistinct chatter]
[Diego] Uncle! Uncle!
-Everyone! Nanny!
-[Loring] Oh, Diego!
-[Pandoy] Diego, you're back.
-I missed you, all!
-We missed you too.
-[Diego] Uncle, how are you?
[chuckling]
-[Diego] Mr. Raul.
-How have you been?
Wait, what brings you to the cooperative?
Aside from wanting to see you all,
-I want to introduce someone.
-Who?
[Loring] Oh! Hold on.
Everyone, meet Miss Camia, Lily's mother.
-[Loring] Oh!
-[Fernan] So, that's her.
-Good day to all of you.
-Ma'am Camia,
it's really you.
How are you?
Ma'am, I saw how you condemned
the Ardientes on TV.
I believe that you are telling the truth.
You need to be careful, Miss Camia.
-Please be safe.
-You don't have to worry
because I have my bodyguards.
And besides, Diego is here to protect me.
[man] Yeah, you can count on Diego.
Of course.
[Diego] I came here
to ask for your support.
Let me be your voice in this town.
Yes, you heard it right.
I, Diego Ardiente-Torillo…
will run for governor
in the next election!
[applause]
[farmer] You deserve
to be the governor, Diego.
Since the beginning,
you've known the hardships
of the townspeople.
We support you. Run, Diego!
Run, Diego! Run, Diego!
Go, Diego!
-Fighting!
-We'll fight with you, Diego!
[applause]
[all] Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
[Ivy] You'll run for governor?
Yes.
I'm the mayor of this town,
so the next logical step
is either to be a governor or a senator.
And I figured that
the Ardiente folks need me.
It's not as if someone
will dare to challenge me.
And I want you by my side…
during the organization…
the filing…
and until the campaign starts.
I would love to, Mr. Mayor.
But…
it will only happen if your mom
and grandpa support us.
As I see it,
they're both against me.
Miss Aguas, no one can oppose me.
No one can decide for me.
And once I become the governor,
I will be the most powerful Ardiente.
[suspenseful sting]
Everyone will bow to the king,
and you…
You will be my queen.
[Julio] You're going to finish
what you started.
Another's head in exchange
for yours, Madrigal.
[Jepoy] I'll do everything to protect you.
I need to save Jepoy. Get out of my way.
-Move out!
-Yes, he's your friend,
but I love you!
Trust me, Ivy. I'll save Jepoy.
I'll bring him back in one piece.
-[Diego] Jepoy, it's me, Diego.
-[grunting]
Ma'am, I've got the files
that you asked for
from the private investigator.
[Emilia] I won't allow my son to be used
by someone who could betray our family.
-What if I kill you right here?
-[Emilia grunts]
-[Arnaldo] Ivy! Stop this!
-[Ivy] Hands off me!
[theme music playing]